A Guide to the William M. Anderson, Jr. Records, 1974-2006
Simpson Library, University of Mary Washington
Special Collections and University Archives, Simpson Library, University of Mary Washington
William M. Anderson, Jr. Records 1974-2006
Special Collections and University Archives, Simpson Library, University of Mary Washington
2006-012
38 record storage boxes (16 linear feet).
Anderson, Jr., William M.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
These materials were transferred from the University President’s Office to the University Archives.
Biographical Information
William M. Anderson, Jr.
President, 1983-2006
Mary Washington College (1983-2004)
University of Mary Washington (2004-2006)
Dr. William M. Anderson, Jr. was born January 15, 1942 in South Boston. As a young man, besides politics, his main interests were music and sports. He earned a Bachelor of Science degree from Virginia Commonwealth University, a master's degree in public administration from West Virginia University College of Graduate Studies, and a doctorate in higher education from Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University. While studying at Virginia Commonwealth University in Richmond, he became acquainted with Prince Woodward, a life-long mentor and eventual President of Mary Washington College, and he also met his future wife, Jane Neale, with whom he had three children. His entire professional career was devoted to higher education, beginning in 1967 when he worked as coordinator of academic programs and enrollment research for the Virginia State Council of Higher Education. Then for four years he served as director of research and planning for the West Virginia Board of Regents. In 1976 he was named Executive Vice President at Mary Washington College before becoming President in 1983.
When Dr. Anderson was appointed president of Mary Washington College in 1983, he was the youngest president of any of Virginia's four-year colleges and universities. Twenty-three years later in 2006, he retired as the longest-serving president of any public institution in Virginia. Among his major achievements at Mary Washington was the creation of the College of Graduate and Professional Studies in Stafford County, which prompted the institution's attainment of university status and an ensuing name change to the University of Mary Washington in 2004.
During his tenure, more than $120 million of capital improvements were made to the University's two campuses, including the addition of a new library, a $14 million science center, a student center, an alumni center, an art gallery, an enclosed campus walk, four new residence halls, and an apartment complex. New cultural offerings for the University and the surrounding community were added during Dr. Anderson's tenure, including programs such as the Fredericksburg Forum, the Great Lives lecture series, and the University of Mary Washington-Community Symphony Orchestra's Celebrity Series. Under Dr. Anderson's administration, the University completed the installation of a campus-wide fiber-optic telecommunications network that brought state-of-the-art data, telephone, and cable service to every classroom, office, and residence hall on campus. Also the intercollegiate athletic program was expanded and a Community Outreach and Resources program was created to promote student volunteerism.
Particularly noteworthy in terms of outreach were Dr. Anderson's efforts to create beneficial ties to the local business community. He was an active member of the Chamber of Commerce, serving at its president, and at his suggestion the University started sponsoring a Business Leaders Breakfast with a visiting Executive in Residence. In addition, during his tenure the University created a Small Business Development Center to support economic development in the area by generating innovative business ideas.
During Dr. Anderson's tenure, and largely because of his energy and efforts, Mary Washington's endowment increased substantially from $1.3 million to $24.5 million, thus contributing not only to enhanced physical facilities, but also to expanded opportunities for faculty development. The result of his work was a significant elevation of Mary Washington's stature to the point of national recognition as a liberal arts and sciences college of outstanding quality, which ranked within the top ten percent nationally in terms of admissions selectivity.
On the occasion of his retirement, numerous individuals and organizations expressed their sincere appreciation for Dr. Anderson's record of achievement at the University of Mary Washington. The Celebrity Concert series at Mary Washington was renamed the William M. Anderson, Jr., Celebrity Concert Series in honor of the support that Dr. Anderson gave to the orchestra. In addition, the General Assembly of Virginia honored Dr. Anderson with a resolution recognizing him "for his long and exceptional service to the students, faculty, staff and alumni of the University of Mary Washington and, moreover, to the people of the Commonwealth of Virginia.” The University of Mary Washington Board of Visitors unanimously approved a resolution naming the school's planned extension to the athletic building the Anderson Convocation Center. During his last commencement ceremony as president, Dr. Anderson was awarded the status of president emeritus and an honorary Doctorate of Humane Letters degree. Also he was presented with the Washington Medallion, which recognizes extraordinary service to the University.
Scope and Content
This collection is arranged into twenty-four main series, in thirty-eight record storage boxes for a total of about 16 linear feet. The first series is senior staff papers from the President's Office during Dr. Anderson's administration. Other series cover commencement records, honor convocation lists, campus buildings and grounds records, annual reports, state of Virginia papers, national educational papers, various university program documents, Southern educational materials, financial records and documents, student affairs materials, special events materials, inauguration papers, Board of Visitors materials, presidential correspondence, various academic committee papers, community relations documents, faculty affairs materials, papers on conferences and workshops, the President's Book Club materials, Dr. Anderson's speeches, and the last series is reserved for miscellaneous materials.
Dr. Anderson and his office compiled or retained this collection, which encompasses various papers, documents and correspondence from throughout his tenure at Mary Washington, mostly as president. The bulk of the items in the collection were gathered from the 1980s to the 1990s. A few of the papers go back as early as 1974, to the years before Dr. Anderson's presidency at Mary Washington. Two folders date to 1969. Among the documents and records are various memos, plans, notes, programs, design sketches, presidential remarks, speeches, invitations, publications, a few cassette tapes, a CD-ROM and some photographs, as well as letters and reports.
Arrangement
The boxes and folders in the collection are arranged by series and further arranged mostly chronologically or alphabetically within the series. There was some original order to the documents, which was followed whenever possible. The provenance of the collection was respected in arranging and describing materials, and the arrangement mostly follows the inventory of materials as they were received: Senior Staff Papers, Recommendations, Commencement Records, Honor Convocation Records, Campus Buildings and Grounds, Annual Reports, State Papers, National Papers, University Papers, Southern Regional Education Records, Southern Association of Colleges and Schools, Financial Affairs, Student Affairs, Events Records, Inauguration, Board of Visitors, President’s Correspondence, Committees, Community Relations, Faculty Affairs, Conferences and Workshops, President’s Book Club, Speeches, and finally Miscellaneous. Documents without apparent order were rearranged according to the inventory by logical series and types of materials.
There was usually some order to the materials, as they were received. All of the folders in the collection were individually arranged within series, based on the inventory list provided, either chronologically or alphabetically. Notebooks and overly large folders were broken down into smaller folders and arranged chronologically, when possible. Each folder was sorted into categories based on the following schema:
Arrangement (Series)
Series 1: Senior Staff Records
Series 2: Recommendations
Series 3: Commencement
Series 4: Honors Convocation
Series 5: Campus Buildings and Grounds
Series 6: Annual Reports
Series 7: State of Virginia Records
Series 8: National Educational Records
Series 9: University Records
Series 10: Southern Regional Education Records
Series 11: Southern Association of Colleges and Schools
Series 12: Financial Affairs
Series 13: Student Affairs
Series 14: Events Records
Series 15: Inauguration
Series 16: Board of Visitors
Series 17: President's Correspondence
Series 18: Committees
Series 19: Community Relations
Series 20: Faculty Affairs
Series 21: Conferences and Workshops
Series 22: President's Book Club
Series 23: Speeches
Series 24: Miscellaneous
Index Terms
Persons:
Anderson, William M., Jr., 1942-
Corporate Names:
Mary Washington College-Fredericksburg (Virginia); University of Mary Washington; University of Mary Washington--History--20th century; University of Mary Washington. Office of the President
Subjects:
College presidents--Virginia; College presidents--Virginia--History--20th century; Education, Higher—Virginia; Universities and Colleges - Administration
Contents List
- Series 1: Senior Staff Records, 1988-2006
  - Senior Staff, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Senior Staff, 1992 January-July (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Senior Staff, 1992 August-November (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Senior Staff, 1992 December (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Senior Staff, 1993 January-February (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Senior Staff, 1993 March-July (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Senior Staff, 1993 August-December (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Senior Staff, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Senior Staff, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Senior Staff, 1996-2006 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Merchent, A.R. - Correspondence, 1990 May-October (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Merchent, A.R. - Correspondence, 1990 November-1991 February (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Warlick, Conrad - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Warlick, Conrad - Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Administrative Roundtable, 1996-2006 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Executive Assistant to the President, 1988 (SOME RESTRICTED MATERIAL) (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Executive Secretary (President's Office), 1990-1992 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Executive Assistant to the President, 1995-1997 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Executive Council, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Special Assistant to the President, 1988-1991 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Administrative Cabinet, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Poyck, Marjorie M., 1989-1991 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Series 2: Recommendations, 1985-2004 (RESTRICTED)
  - Recommendations, 1985-1990 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Recommendations, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Recommendations, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Recommendations, 1993-1995 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Recommendations, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Recommendations, 2002-2004 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Series 3: Commencement Records, 1993-2006
  - Commencement, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Commencement, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Commencement, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Commencement, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Design Sketch for Presidential Collar, Commencement, 2006 (Note: located in Oversize Archives Map Case) (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Series 4: Honor Convocation Records, 1989-1996
  - Honor Convocation, 1989 August (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Honor Convocation, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Honor Convocation, 1991 August 25 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Honor Convocation, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Honor Convocation, 1993 August 22 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Honor Convocation, 1994 August 21 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Honor Convocation, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Series 5: Campus Buildings and Grounds, 1968-1996
  - Brompton Kitchen, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Combs Hall/Allyson Gallery, 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Goolrick Portrait, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Palmieri Plaza, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Trinkle Library, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - William Street Parking Lot, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - William Street Traffic Signal, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Dodd Auditorium, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Landfill, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Audio-Visual Center, 1977-1983 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Sand Runoff, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Soil and Erosion Review, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - George Washington Hall, 1968-1983 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Buildings and Grounds Superintendent, 1976-1982 (SOME RESTRICTED MATERIALS) (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Ann Carter Lee Hall, 1969-1982 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Campus Center, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Child Care Center, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Art Gallery, Groundbreaking, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Student Center - Library, Groundbreaking and Dedication, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Historic Preservation, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Moratorium - Sewer, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Multicultural Center, 1990-1992 (SOME RESTRICTED MATERIAL) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Campus Map, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Physical Plant Report, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Pool Incident, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Post Office, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Sunshine Laundry Property, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Land Transactions, 1977-1990 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Easement - Cimmino Property, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Series 6: Annual Reports, 1982-1996
  - Annual Reports, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Annual Reports, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Annual Reports, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Annual Reports, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Trinkle Library, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Series 7: State of Virginia Records, 1974-1995
  - Commission of the University of the 21st Century, 1988-1991 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Council of Higher Education, 1985-1993 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Decentralization, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - State of Higher Education for Virginia, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Cool Project, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Register, 1991-1995 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Commission to Study Historic Preservation, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Association of Virginia Colleges and Universities, 1987-1990 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Chamber of Commerce Leadership Education Session, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Civility Meeting, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Alliance for Sheltered Housing for Retarded Citizens, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Chancellorsville Commissioning Committee, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Commonwealth Centers, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Virginia Four-Year Public College Substance Abuse Prevention Consortium, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Chesapeake Bay Agreement, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Council of Higher Education for Virginia Grant Proposals: "Improving Human Relationships on College Campuses", 1990 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Council of Higher Education Funds for Excellence, 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Council of Presidents (Competitive Edge Proposal), 1989 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Council of Presidents, 1980-1985 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Davies, Gordon - Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Disaster Plan, 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Executive Memorandum 1-88 "Make or Buy", 1989 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Freedom of Information Act Seminar, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - General Assembly, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - General Assembly, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Project Streamline, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Register Act, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - IPAC - Working File, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - JLARC: "Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission", 1983 (SOME RESTRICTED MATERIAL) (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Rick Kast - Attorney General's Office, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Memorandum of Understanding, "1984-86 Biennium", 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Executive Order Number One (90), 1990 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Virginia Higher Education Funding, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Series 8: National Records, 1989-1996
  - Council of Public Liberal Arts Colleges (COPLAC), 1996 June 23 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - [United States Information Agency] USIA, 1995 April 13 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - American Association of State Colleges and Universities (AASCU), 1989-1991 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Series 9: University Records, 1969-1996
  - Eminent Scholars Program, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Kenmore Association, 1994-1996 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Telecommunications, 1994, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Weinbrecht, Ruby, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Applicants, 1985 (SOME RESTRICTED MATERIAL) (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Administrative Evaluation, 1988 (SOME RESTRICTED MATERIAL) (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Foley, Arthur P., 1989 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Academic Computing, 1980-1989 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Leasing Equipment, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Race and Gender Project, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Restructured Teacher Preparation Plan, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - S.A.T. Information - Freshman Class of 1983 and 1984 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - C&W Associates, Inc.: Final Report to President and Cabinet, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - TV Coverage, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Upward Bound Project, 1979-1980 (SOME RESTRICTED MATERIAL) (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Upward Bound Project, 1981-1987 (SOME RESTRICTED MATERIAL) (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Statements (Community Values and Non-discrimination), 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Admissions and Financial Aid, 1974-1983 (SOME RESTRICTED MATERIAL) (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Calendar for MWC, 1969-1991 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Civility Actions, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Consultant Contracts, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Dahlgren Meeting, 1990-1992 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Enrollment, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Restructuring Plan: "Building on a Tradition of Educational Excellence", 1994 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - OCN (Office Communications Network), 1990-1994 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Office of International Programs, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Ombudspersons, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Minority Recruitment and Retention, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Recruit and Retain, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - James Farmer Scholars Program, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Series 10: Southern Regional Education Records, 1989-1992
  - Board of Control, 1989-1990 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Board of Control, 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Southern Regional Education Board Conference, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - SREB Meeting, 1992 June 27-30 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Series 11: Southern Association of Colleges and Schools (SACS), 1988-2004
  - Florida Gulf Coast University, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Response to the "Report of the Reaffirmation Committee", 2003 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Report of the Reaffirmation Committee, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - SACS Visit Recommendations (In Draft Form), 2003 March 25-28 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - First Follow-Up Report, SACS, 2004 September (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools, 2003-2004 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Series 12: Financial Affairs, 1983-1996
  - Germanna Community College, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - President's Discretionary Funds, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - President's Unrestricted Fund, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Hamer Music Fund, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - MWC Foundation, 1983-1985 (SOME RESTRICTED MATERIAL) (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - DuPont Fund, 1985-1991 (SOME RESTRICTED MATERIAL) (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Equipment Trust Fund, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Locality Bills, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Merit Pay, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Hofer Fund, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Regional Scholarship Program, 1991-1993 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Series 13: Student Affairs, 1983-1999
  - Chamber Music Festival, 1988-1989 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Dean's List, 1982-1983, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Student Escort Service, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Krauss Report, 1997-1999 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - President's List, 1987-1989 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Housing, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Mary Siegrist Hinz Leadership Award, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Junior Ring Presentation Ceremony, 1984-1990 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Homecoming, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Honors Day, 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Student Opinion Survey, 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Student Dorm (New), 1989 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Wo-Man Contest, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Student Center, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Sports Information Reports, 1989 February-April (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Visitation, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Rugby, 1985-1987 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Student Association, 1987-1989 (Note: contains photographs) (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Student Association, 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Student Association Officers, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Student Association, 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Student Association, 1992-1993 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Student Senate, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Student Transition Program, 1986-1991 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Series 14: Events Records, 1983-1995
  - Levitt, Alfred (exhibit), 1994 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Christ Church Address, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - CUIDES (Inter-American University Council for Economic and Social Development) Meeting, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Music Camp (proposal), 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Family Weekend, 1983-1987 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Nation of Islam, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Opening Ceremonies, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Religious Freedom Day (Thomas Jefferson Institute), 1984-1995 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Jepson Celebration, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Series 15: Inauguration, 1983-1984
  - Committee Meetings and Plans, 1983-1984 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Congratulations, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Inauguration - Correspondence, 1983 November-1984 May (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Inaugural Address, 1984 April 7 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Inauguration - News Clippings (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Inauguration - Videos (Note: see other location, S3.I.) (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Invitations and Programs (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Series 16: Board of Visitors, 1976-1997
  - Castles, General John G., 1976-1988 (SOME RESTRICTED MATERIAL) (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Memos to Board of Visitors from Public Information Office, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Board of Visitors Memos, 1997 January-May (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Board of Visitors Memos, 1997 June-December (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Board of Visitors Memos, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Board of Visitors Memos, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Board of Visitors Memos, 1994 September-December (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Board of Visitors Memos, 1994 February-May (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Board of Visitors Memos, 1994 June-August (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Student Association President (Student Representative to Board of Visitors), 1986-1990 (SOME RESTRICTED MATERIAL) (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Series 17: President's Correspondence, 1980-2006 (RESTRICTED MATERIAL INTERFILED -all folders in series)
  - President's Correspondence, 1982-1985 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - President's Correspondence, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - President's Correspondence, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - President's Correspondence, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - President's Correspondence, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - President's Correspondence, 1994 January-June (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - President's Correspondence, 1994 July-December (Box 17, Folder 7)